If you had to start from scratch,
for some reason someone comes along and wipes you off
the face of the earth, and
then you say, "Damn, I wake up, you have
today's skills, what can you do?"
Well, and I think it's a lot of
fun to be a builder these days.
At the beginning of Banding Spong I was working
on the development, on the code and it's
very frustrating, no, that you have
the idea in your head and yet computers are
so stupid, pardon the expression, that you
have to tell them in detail,
so when the window opens
do this and then the button, then connect
the logic and so this idea of ​​being able to
work at the abstraction level of the
functionality, the features, the value
to be created for users and and
then being able to delegate to the AI ​​the task of
making them concrete is very cool right now
the human factor, that is, the
understanding of users, the fact of
knowing that if you do things in a certain
way it will have a certain result, if you do them
differently it will have another.  She can
try to give you an opinion, but very
often she's wrong and so you need
the human and I'm very curious how long it
will continue to be like this, but right
now it is and as long as it is like this it's a
fantastic time to be a
builder.  Today you have a favorite product
of all the products you have.
Well, it's a bit like when you say
you have a preference for one child
over another, [laughter]
but a product that I've always
really enjoyed is WeTransfer and by
the way I feel sorry for the We
Transfer team, I really stressed them out
because I was suggesting it to them precisely
because I like it so much, I
was offering them a lot of ideas on how to
improve it.  At one point they say to me,
"Matt, stop breaking my balls."